Guide to the Yale University Press Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Published book files, 1986-2017; Accession 2018-A-0040
  - Collins/It is Daylight, 2007-2009 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Collins/The Nile, 1997-2010 (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
  - Comer/Leave No Child Behind, 2002-2005 (Box 17, Folder 6-7)
  - Abramowicz/Marketocracy, 2005-2007 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Ackerman/Just Words, 2009-2010 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Ambramowitz/The Disappearing Center, 2007-2010 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Agee, Sandler, and Wilkin/American Vanguards, 2010-2011 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Anderson/The Play of Fiction, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Ahmed/Quiet Revolution, 2009-2011 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Arrow/Social Choice and Individual Value, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Auchincloss and Sandberg/Psychoanalytic Terms and Concepts, 2009-2013 (Box 17, Folder 15-16)
  - Berenson/Statue of Liberty, 2008-2011 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Bicllah and Lemigru/Leningrad, 2008-2012 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Bidlack et. al/The Leningrad Blockade, 1941-1944, 1998-2010 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Blanton/Integrating the Mexican American, 2012-2014 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Bloom/The Shadow ofa Great Rock: A Literary Appreciation of the King James Bible, 2010-2011 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - Bloom/The Anatomy of Influence, 2010-2011 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Bowker/The Message and the Book, 2010-2011 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Brandenberger/Stalin's Catechism and the Propaganda State, 2009-2011 (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
  - Buck/Acting White, 2005-2010 (Box 18, Folder 7-8)
  - Britton/Constructing the Ineffable, 2007-2008 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Brown and Ben-Atar/Sexual Transgressions, 2007-2008 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Carey/From Peace to Freedom, 2011-2013 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Carmichael/The Book of Numbers as a Critique of Genesis, 2011-2012 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Charyn/Joe Dimaggio (American Icons), 2006-2010 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Clark and Strauss/Shifting Paradigms in Contemporary Ceramics, 2010-2011 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Clark/Abraham's Children, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Clapp et. al/Law Talk volume 1, 2001-2008 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Clapp et. al/Law Talk volume 2, 2001-2011 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Chase/Introduction to Spanish for Health Care Workers, 2011-2015 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Cole/Poetry of the Kabbalah, 2010-2012 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Coinsbee/Cezanne in Provence, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Coinsbee/French Genre Painting, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Conlon/The Essential Hospital Handbook, 2007-2009 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Connor/Women in Byzantium, 1997-2005 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Cook/Matters of Exchange, 2003-2007 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Cook/Matters of Exchange-Permissions, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Coo/Beautiful Province, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Cook/Alfred Kazin: A Biography, 1994-2010 (Box 18, Folder 27-29)
  - Cook/Kazin's Journal, 2010-2011 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Cooper/Frank Stella 1958, 2004-2006 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Cooper and Heckler/Medardo Rosso: Second Impressions, 2004-2006 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Cooper/Searching for Shakespeare, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Copquin/The Neighborhood of Queens, 2002-2007 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Cox/The Big House: Image and Reality of the American Prison, 2008-2010 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Coyle and Schiller/John Sloan's New York, 2006-2007 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Cowan/The Social Life of Coffee, 2003-2006 (Box 19, Folder 9-10)
  - Corral/Slow Lightning, 2010-2012 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Corns/The Milton Encyclopedia, 2002-2012 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Corbett/Boyhoods: Rethinking Masculinities, 2008-2009 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Craig and Radchenko/The Atomic Bomb and the Origins of the Cold War, 2003-2008 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Cramer/I to Myself, 2004-2008 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Cramer/Maine Woods, 2006-2009 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Cramer/Walden: A Fully Annotated Edition, 2002-2007 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Crawford/Windfall of Musicians, 1997-2009 (Box 19, Folder 18-19)
  - Crosby/Affirmative Action is Dead, 2001-2004 (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
  - Crow/The Rise of the 60s, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Cullen/Caribbean: Art at the Crossroads of the World, 2010-2012 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Cumings/Dominion from Sea to Sea, 1999-2009 (Box 20, Folder 6-8)
  - Cunningham/The Artistic Furniture of Charles Rohlfs, 2007-2008 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Cusac/Cruel and Unusual Punnishment in America, 2004-2009 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Dahl/The American Constitution, 2000-2003 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Dahl/Who Governs? Second Edition, 2003-2004 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Dahl/On Political Equality, 2005-2007 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Daigle/The Limits of Détente, 2010-2011 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Dallal/Islam and Science, 2007-2009 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Dallas/1945: The War that Never Ended, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Dalismer/Virginia Woolf: Becoming a Writer, 1995-2001 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Dalton/Taming of Demons, 2008-2011 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Daniell/Every Other Thursday, 2004-2006 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Danto/Andy Warhol, 2007-2010 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Danly/Georgia O'Keefe and the Camera, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Daniels/The Rise and Fall of Communism in Russia, 2001-2008 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Davidson/A Little History of the United States, 2011-2015 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Davies et. al/The Stalin-Kaganovich Correspondence, 1931-1936, 1997-2003 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Davis/The Art of Frederick Sommer, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Davis/Origins of American Philosophy, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Davis and Renner/Penguins: Living in Two Worlds, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Deater-Decker/Parenting Stress, 2001-2005 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - De Haven/Our Hero: Superman on Earth, 2005-2009 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Delay/War of a Thousand Deserts, 2004-2007 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Delfattore/Knowledge in the Making, 1995-2010 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Delfattore/The Fourth R: The Politics of Religion in American Schools, 1995-2004 (Box 21, Folder 10-11)
  - Demaray/the Invention of Dante's Commedia, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - De Mul/The Tragedy of Finitude, 1994-2005 (Box 21, Folder 13-14)
  - Dickinson/Outsourcing War and Peace, 2009-2010 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Delmez/Carrie Mae Weems, 2010-2011 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Denenberg/Call of the Coast, 2008-2009 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Denenberg/Wallace Nutting and the Invention of Old America, 2001-2003 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - de Rojas/Celestina, 2007-2009 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Dershowitz/Why Terrorism Works, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Derys/Mon Docteur Le Vin, 2003-2004 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Desdimaines/Stepping Stones, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - de Vega/Fuento Ovejuna, 2009-2010 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Devigne/Reforming Liberalism, 2004-2005 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - de Zegher and Sussman/Eva Hesse Drawings, 2005-2006 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Dien/Six Dynasties Civilization, 1983-2004 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Dimoula/Selected Poetry, 2008-2012 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Dimoula/The Brazen Plagarist, 2008-2012 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Dobrenko/Political Economy of Socialist Realism, 2006-2007 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Dobrenko/Stalinist Cinema and the Production of History, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Doezema and Milroy/Reading in American Art-Permissions, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 13-18)
  - Dohner/The Encyclopedia of Historic and Endangered Livestock and Poultry Breeds, 1996-2005 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Dolidon/Tu Sais Quoi?, 2010-2012 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Donahue/The Great Meadow, 1998-2004 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Donahue/Deutsche Weiderholungsgrammatik, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Donaldson et. al/Careers in Medicine, 2000-2002 (Box 23, Folder 2-3)
  - Donnelly and Straus/Corporal Punnishment of Children in Theoretical Perspective, 1998-2005 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Donoghue/the American Classic, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Donoghue/Speaking of Beauty, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Dostoevsky/The Meek One ed. (Titus), 2009-2011 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Doty/Cuneiform Documents-Yale Oriental Series, 2011 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Douglas/Thinking in Circles, 2005-2007 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Douglas/The Expulsion of the Germans, 2009-2011 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Dove/The Banana Tree at the Gate, 2008-2010 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Dreys/Mon Docteur-emails, 2002-2004 (Box 23, Folder 12-16)
  - Drinan/Can God and Caesar Coexist?, 2002-2007 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - DuDove/Life Past Present and Future, 2008-2010 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Dudzinski and Fronoff/Dolphin Mysteries, 2005-2008 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Dunbar/A Fragile Freedom, 2003-2008 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Duncan/The Reason Machine, 2008-2010 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Duran and Rogg/Fighting Windmills, 2002-2006 (Box 24, Folder 4-5)
  - Dwyer/Citizen Emperor, 2007-2013 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Dwyer/Napoleon: The Path to Power, 1769-1799, 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Dykstra et. al/Schreiben Lernen, 2009-2015 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Dyson/The History of Classical Archaeology, 2001-2006 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Eagleton/Why Marx was Right, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Eagleton/On Evil, 2008-2010 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Eakins/The Drawing Manual of Thomas Eakins, 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Earle/Aaron Douglas: African American Modernist, 2005-2007 (Box 24, Folder 13-14)
  - Earle/Serizawa: Master of Japanese Textile Design, 2008-2009 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Echevarria/Cuban Fiestas, 2006-2010 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Edelman/Second Nature, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Edelman/Wider Than the Sky, 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Edlow/Study in Scarlet and other Detective Stories, 2003-2008 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Gonzalez/Love and Law in Cervantes, 2004-2008 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Edlow/Bull's Eye, 2000-2004 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Edwards/Why the Electoral College is Bad For America, 1999-2006 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Egan/Getting it Wrong From the Beginning, 2000-2004 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Egan/The Future of Education: Reimagining our Schools From the Ground-Up, 1998-2008 (Box 25, Folder 4-5)
  - Eger and Peltz/Brilliant Women: 18th Century Bluestockings, 2007-2008 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Ehernfeld/Sustainability by Design, 2006-2008 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Ehrman/The Eighties, 1999-2006 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Einstein and McDaniel/Memory Fitness, 1999-2006 (Box 25, Folder 9-10)
  - Eire/Reformations: Early Modern Europe, 1450-1650, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Eisenman/Eisenman Inside-Out, 2000-2004 (Box 25, Folder 12-13)
  - Eisenman/Eisenman Essays vol. 2, 2004-2006 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Eisner/The Arts and the Creation of the Mind, 2001-2005 (Box 25, Folder 15-16)
  - Eklund/Thomas Struth, 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Elliott/Bye Bye Kitty, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Eliot/The Letters of T.S. Eliot vol. 1 and 2, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Elliott/Singing in Style, 1997-2007 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Elkins/Blue Yodel, 2014-2015 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Ellis/Kant Politics, 2002-2008 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Ellison et. al/A Field Guide to the Ants of New England, 2010-2014 (Box 26, Folder 6-7)
  - Eltis and Richardson/Atlas of the Transatlantic Slave Trade, 2006-2010 (Box 26, Folder 8-12)
  - Eltis and Richardson/Extending the Frontiers: Essays on the New Transatlantic Slave Trade, 2006-2008 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Engelking and Leociak/The Warsaw Ghetto, 2004-2012 (Box 26, Folder 14-15)
  - Engell et. al/Environment: An Interdisciplinary Anthology vol. 2, 1999-2007 (Box 26, Folder 16-17)
  - Engell et. al/Environment: An Interdisciplinary Anthology vol. 3, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Ensmiger/Life Under the Sun, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Epstein/Fred Astaire-Icons of America, 2007-2009 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Epstein/Overdose, 2005-2006 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Epstein/Psychotherapy Without the Self, 2006-2008 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Epstein/The Medieval Illuminated Haggadah, 2009-2011 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Erofeev/Walpurgis Night, or the Steps of the Commander, 2009-2013 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Etsy and Winston/Green to Gold, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Etzioni/Security First, 2006-2007 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Evans/Many are Called, 2003-2005 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Everett/Sigmund Bomberg, 2001-2008 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Fairbanks/Papermaking and the Art of Watercolor in 18th Century Britain, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Fairhead/The Captain and the "Cannibal", 2013-2015 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Fairlie/Bite the Hand That Feeds You, 2008-2009 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Falvey/Medicine at Yale: First 200 Years, 2009-2010 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Fanger/Gorky's Tolstoy and other Reminiscences, 1998-2008 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Faragher/Women and Men on the Overland Trail, 1999-2001 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Faragher and Hine/Frontiers: A Short History of the American West, 1998-2007 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Farndon/Atlas of Oceans, 2009-2010 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Farnham/Saving Nature's Legacy, 2004-2007 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Fassler/Making History: The Liturgical Framework of Time and the Cult of the Virgin of Chatres, 1000-1194, 1998-2011 (Box 27, Folder 21-23)
  - Fasulo/Insider's Guide to the UN, 2002-2005 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Fasulo/Insider's Guide to the UN vol. 2, 2007-2009 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Faulkner/The Case of Greatness, 2006-2008 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Fawcett-Tang: New Typographic Design, 2007-2009 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Faye/Heidigger: The Introduction of Nazism Into Philosophy-Translated by Michael B. Smith, 2006-2009 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Feder/Gustav Mahler: A Life in Crisis, 2000-2008 (Box 28, Folder 4-5)
  - Feiner/Moses Mendelssohn, 2009-2010 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Feist/The Psychology of Science, 1999-2009 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Feduccia/Riddle of the Feathered Dragon, 1999-2011 (Box 28, Folder 8-9)
  - Fellman/In the Name of God and Country, 2003-2009 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Felsteiner/Can Poetry Save the Earth?, 2007-2009 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Fennell/Unbounded Home, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Ferguson/The Sage of Sugar Hill, 2003-2005 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Fermi/Elementary Particles, 2011 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Field/A Great Leap Forward, 2008-2011 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Fiese/Family Routines and Rituals, 2003-2006 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Fineberg/Christo and Jean-Claude: The Gates, 2003-2004 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Fineberg and Carlin/Imagining America, 2002-2005 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Findley/Trukey, Islam, Nationalism and Modernity, 1998-2010 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Finkel/On The Ideological Front, 2005-2010 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Firor and Jacobsen/The Crowded Greenhouse, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 3-4)
  - Firmat/The Havana Habit, 2008-2010 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Fisher/Frail-Craft, 2006-2007 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Fisher/Nutcracker Nation, 1999-2003 (Box 29, Folder 7-10)
  - Fisher/Picasso and the Allure of Language, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Fitzgerald/Every Farm a Factory, 1999-2003 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Fitzgerald/Picasso and American Art, 2005-2006 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Foer/A Voter's Guide: Election 2008, 2005-2007 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Fogelson/Bourgeois Nightmare: Suburbia, 2004-2006 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Fogelson/Downtown: Its Rise and Fall, 2000-2003 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Fontaine/Double Life, 2011-2012 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Forcione/Majesty and Humanity, 2006-2008 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Ford/Trouble with City Planning, 2006-2010 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Fort/Prophet, Profits and Peace, 2007-2008 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Foster and Aber/Forests in Time, 2000-2004 (Box 30, Folder 1-4)
  - Foster and Kreitman/Rhythms of Life, 2003-2005 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Foster and Kreitman/Seasons of Life, 2005-2009 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Frangieh/Intro to Arab Culture, 2004-2005 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Frangieh/Arabic for Life, 2007-2009 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Frank/readings in Latin American Modern Art, 2002-2004 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Frank/Fighting Cancer with Knowledge and Hope, 2007-2013 (Box 30, Folder 10-11)
  - Frankel and De Pace/Visual Strategies for Scientists and Engineers, 2010-2012 (Box 30, Folder 12-14)
  - Franklin: James Fenimore Cooper: The Early Years, 2004-2016 (Box 30, Folder 15-16)
  - Franks/The Tiger's Eye, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Fraser/Wall Street: America's Dream Palace, 2007-2009 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Freamon et. al/Slavery and the Slave Trades in the Indian Ocean World, 2009-2013 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Street/Preaching in the New Millenium, 2003-2005 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Frederickson/Ancient Philosophy, 2008-2010 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Fredriksen/Augustine and the Jews, 2009-2010 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Freedman/Flavor and Fashion: Spices in the Middle Ages, 2004-2008 (Box 31, Folder 5-6)
  - Freeman/Affairs of Honor, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Freeman et. al/Managing for Stakeholders, 2006-2007 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Freeman/John Payne Collier: Scholarship and Forgery in the 19th Century, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Freeman and Freeman/John Payne Collier: The Scholar-Forger and His Circle, 2000-2004 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - French/New Urban Housing, 2004-2006 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Freyfogle/Why Conservation is Failing, 2004-2005 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Friedlander/Franz Kafka: the Poet of Shame and Guilt, 2007-2013 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Friedman/American Glamour and the Evolution of Modern Architecture, 2006-2009 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Friedman/American Law in the 20th Century, 1997-2004 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Friedman et. al/Revolution, Resistance and Rerform in Village China, 2000-2008 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Friedman/Women and the Making of the Modern House, 2004-2007 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Freiman/Maria Magdalena Campos-Pons, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Friel/The Lomborg Deception, 2009-2010 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Frierson/Children of the Gulag, 2004-2008 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Frost/Bering: The Russian Discovery of America, 2002-2009 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Fry/The Theory of Literature, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Fry/Wordsworth and the Poetry of What We Are, 2007-2009 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Fu, Steinhardt et. al/Chinese Architecture, 2002-2004 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Fukuyama/America at the Crossroads, 2005-2006 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Gabler/Barbara Steisand, 2014-2016 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Gac/Singing for Freedom, 2004-2007 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Galilei/Dialogue on Ancient and Modern Music, 1998-2002 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Galor et. al/Archaeology of Jerusalem, 2002-2005 (Box 32, Folder 9-10)
  - Gallagher/Vatican Secret Diplomacy, 2005-2008 (Box 32, Folder 11-12)
  - Gallay/The Indian Slave Trade, 1999-2003 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Gambrell/Earthly Signs, 1996-2002 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Gann/No Such Thing As Silence: John Cage's 4x33, 2007-2010 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Ganz and Kendall/The Unknown Monet, 2006-2007 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Gao Xingjian/The Case for Literature, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Garbarini/Numbered Days: Diaries and the Holocaust, 2006-2009 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Garbutt/Mammals of Madagascar: A Complete Guide, 2006-2007 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Gareau/From Precaution to Profit, 2010-2013 (Box 32, Folder 21-22)
  - Garfinkle/The American Dream and the Gospel of Wealth, 2005-2006 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Garfinkle/United America, 2004-2007 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Garland/Italian Paintings, 2002-2003 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Garlock/Felix Candela, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Garrett/No Ordinary Angel, 2006-2009 (Box 33, Folder 5)